spreecast.com 2015-12-23

# Privacy Policy – About Spreecast

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Spreecast Inc. or its subsidiaries or affiliated companies.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at [support@spreecast.com](mailto:support@spreecast.com).

Spreecast  
582 Market Street, Suite 2002  
San Francisco, CA 94104  
(415)369-9314

**Information we collect and how we use it**  
We may collect the following types of information:

**Information you provide** – When you sign up for a Spreecast Account, we ask you for personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Spreecast services or third parties in order to provide a better experience and to improve the quality of our services.

**Cookies** – When you visit Spreecast, we may send one or more cookies or other files to your computer or other device. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences, improving search results and ad selection, and tracking user trends, such as how people search. Spreecast may also use cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web and on Spreecast services.

**Log information** – When you access Spreecast services via a browser, application or other client our servers automatically record certain information. These server logs may include information such as your web request, your interaction with a service, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser or your account.

**User communications** – When you send email or other communications to Spreecast, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. When you send and receive SMS messages to or from one of our services that provides SMS functionality, we may collect and maintain information associated with those messages, such as the phone number, the wireless carrier associated with the phone number, the content of the message, and the date and time of the transaction. We may use your email address to communicate with you about our services.

**Third Party Applications** – Spreecast may make available third party applications, such as gadgets or extensions, through its services. The information collected by Spreecast when you enable a third party application is processed under this Privacy Policy. Information collected by the third party application provider is governed by their privacy policies.

**Location data** – Spreecast may offer location-enabled services. If you use those services, Spreecast may receive information about your actual location (such as GPS signals sent by a mobile device) or information that can be used to approximate a location (such as a cell ID).

**Other sites** – This Privacy Policy applies to Spreecast services only. We do not exercise control over the sites that include Spreecast applications, products or services, or links from within our various services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

In addition to the above, we may use the information we collect to:

Provide, maintain, protect, and improve our services (including advertising services) and develop new services; and

Protect the rights or property of Spreecast or our users.

If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

Spreecast processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information outside your own country.

**Opt-out Choices**  
Should you choose to opt-out of being contacted by Spreecast for any reason, you can use the Spreecast Privacy Controls found in the “Privacy” section under “Account” on the Spreecast site to review and control your privacy settings. To find your account settings, log in to Spreecast and click the “Account” link under your username in the upper right hand corner of the page.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Spreecast features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

**Childrens’ Privacy**  
Spreecast does not knowingly collect information from children under 13 years of age. The Spreecast service is intended for a general audience and is not in any way targeted to children under 13 years of age. If any parent, guardian, or other person becomes aware that a child under the age of 13 has submitted any information to Spreecast or Spreecast has otherwise posted or obtained any information about a child under the age of 13, please notify us by emailing us at customerservice@spreecast.com or call us at (415) 369-9314 and we will take appropriate steps to remove and/or delete the information.

**Information sharing**  
Spreecast only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Spreecast in the following limited circumstances:

We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.

We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Spreecast, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

If Spreecast becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, your personal information may be transferred and become subject to a different privacy policy. We will notify you if and when any such transaction is completed if we have a valid email address for you.

**Information security**  
We restrict access to personal information to Spreecast employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it on our behalf. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page. Your continued use of the Spreecast services signifies your compliance with the then-current privacy policy.

**Personal Information**  
**Browsing Spreecast** You can watch video content on Spreecast without having a Spreecast Account. You also can contact us by emailing us directly without having to register for an account.

**Your Spreecast Account.** For some activities on Spreecast, like creating a show or broadcast or making comments, you need a Spreecast Account. We ask for some personal information when you create an account, including your email address and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.

**Usage Information.** When you use Spreecast, we may record information about your usage of the site, such as the channels, broadcasts, and users that you follow, which other users you communicate with, the shows and broadcasts you watch, the frequency and size of data transfers, and information you display about yourself as well as information you click on in Spreecast (including UI elements, settings, ad advertisements). If you are logged in, we may associate that information with your Spreecast Account. In order to ensure the quality of our service to you, we may place a cookie or tag (also called a “web beacon”) in HTML-based customer support emails or other communications with you in order to confirm delivery.

**Content Uploaded to Site.** Any personal information or video content that you voluntarily disclose online (e.g., video comments, your profile page) may be collected and used by others.

**Public Live Shows are Recorded.** All of the public live shows on Spreecast are recorded and will be available for playback. Other users will be able to come to Spreecast.com and playback any public shows you created on the site or through the Spreecast products or services.

**Uses**  
If you submit personal information to Spreecast, we may use that information to operate, maintain, and improve the features and functionality of Spreecast, and to process any flagging activity, broadcasts or other communication you send to us.

We may use your email address or other personal information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent. We may also use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as notifying you of major Spreecast changes or for customer service purposes).

We use cookies, web beacons, and log file information to: (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit Spreecast; (b) provide custom, personalized content, information, and advertisements; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

**Information That is Publicly Available**  
When you create a Spreecast Account, some information about your Spreecast Account and your account activity will be provided to other users of Spreecast. This may include the date you opened your Spreecast Account, the date you last logged into your Spreecast Account, the Content you have created, the number of followers you have, the people and channels that you are following, the country you are from and the number of videos you have watched.

Your Spreecast Account name, not your email address, is displayed to other users when you engage in certain activities on Spreecast, such as when you create a show or send messages through Spreecast. Other users can contact you by leaving a message or comment on the site.

Any videos that you submit to Spreecast, broadcasts you originate, or other Content on Spreecast may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels, and may be viewed by other Spreecast users or the general public.

You may also choose to add personal information which may include your name, gender, profile picture or other details, that will be visible to other users on your Spreecast Profile page.

**Your Choices**  
If you have a Spreecast Account, you may update or correct your personal profile information, email preferences and privacy settings at any time by visiting your account profile page.

You may control the information that is available to other users at any time by editing your Spreecast privacy settings.

You may, of course, decline to submit personal information through Spreecast, in which case you can still view videos or broadcasts and explore Spreecast, but Spreecast may not be able to provide certain services to you.

**Advertising on Spreecast**  
Spreecast strives to provide you with relevant and useful advertising. We may use a range of information including cookies, web beacons, IP addresses, usage data and other information about your activity online, computer or device (such as browser type and operating system) or other information to provide you with relevant advertising. While you are logged in or logged out of your Spreecast Account, we may also show you advertising based on information you have provided to us in your Spreecast Account.

We may use various cookies on Spreecast to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads on this site and other Spreecast products and services. Advertisers may serve ads based on interests and demographic categories associated with non-personally identifiable online activity, such as videos viewed, shows created or other activity. Advertisers may also serve ads to you based on previous activity on that advertiser’s website or based on non-personally identifiable information from other companies.

Other third-party ad serving companies may display ads on Spreecast. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks for more information on their practices and for instructions on how to opt-out of certain practices. Spreecast’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. Any data obtained by third-party ad servers subsequently shared with Spreecast is maintained and dealt with by Spreecast in accordance with this privacy policy.

**More Information**  
By submitting any Content or personal information to Spreecast, you acknowledge that you are submitting the information to the United States and it is collected and maintained in the United States. For questions concerning the product or your account, please check out the help content.

For more information about our privacy practices, email us at [support@spreecast.com](mailto:support@spreecast.com).
